<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Don Figuerres</title><link>https://donfiguerres.com/</link><description>Recent content on Don Figuerres</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 23:34:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://donfiguerres.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Common Tools for Software Development</title><link>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/software-development/common-tools/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 23:34:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/software-development/common-tools/</guid><description>List of tools that I&amp;rsquo;ve used throughout my development career that you might find useful too. I use this list when setting up a new VM or workstation.
Browser Google Chrome It&amp;rsquo;s most people&amp;rsquo;s default browser although Edge has a better performance in Windows. Brave Browser I use this personally for browsing. It has a lot of default privacy features. Can be used to test if a website will continue to function if all the security and privacy features are enabled.</description></item><item><title>Java Performance Testing Using Zerocode</title><link>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/software-development/java/java-performance-testing-using-zerocode/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 23:10:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/software-development/java/java-performance-testing-using-zerocode/</guid><description>In one of my previous projects, I had to add a performance testing suite for our Java APIs to measure the performance gain in the performance improvement that I was working on.
After some research, I found that Zerocode is able to fulfill our needs. Their GitHub Repo also includes an extensive documentation which made the process much easier for me.
I found that you can reuse your existing JUnit tests as performance tests using the LoadWith annotation.</description></item><item><title>Git Connection Errors During Cloning</title><link>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/version-control/git/git-connection-errors-during-cloning/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 17:18:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/version-control/git/git-connection-errors-during-cloning/</guid><description>I got these errors recently when I was trying to clone one of our repos. Unstable network connection or network infrastructure may have caused this so as a workaround, you can clone the repo &amp;ldquo;bit-by-bit&amp;rdquo;.
$ git clone ssh://git@your.host.com/yourrepo.git Cloning into &amp;#39;projectdir&amp;#39;... ... remote: Enumerating objects: 26639, done. remote: Counting objects: 100% (269/269), done. remote: Compressing objects: 100% (152/152), done. client_loop: send disconnect: Connection reset by peer6 MiB/s fetch-pack: unexpected disconnect while reading sideband packet fatal: fetch-pack: invalid index-pack output $ git clone ssh://git@your.</description></item><item><title>Changing Committer, Author, and Email in Git</title><link>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/version-control/git/changing-committer-author-and-email-in-git/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:12:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/version-control/git/changing-committer-author-and-email-in-git/</guid><description>I recently observed in my GitHub profile that most of my commits are not shown in my contribution activity. After doing a quick search, I found that the problem because my email in my commits do not match the email associated with my GitHub account.
Changing Commits in the Remote Repository You need to use the filter-branch command to change the emails and names.
git filter-branch -f --env-filter &amp;#39; GIT_AUTHOR_NAME=&amp;#34;yourname&amp;#34;; GIT_AUTHOR_EMAIL=&amp;#34;youremaill@host.</description></item><item><title>Factorial</title><link>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/programming-tutorials/factorial/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 02:57:52 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/programming-tutorials/factorial/</guid><description>Factorial is the product of all positive integers less than or equal to a given positive integer and denoted by that integer and an exclamation point.
n! = n * (n-1) * (n-2) * (n-3) ... 3 * 2 * 1 For example
5! = 5 * 4 * 3 * 2 * 1 = 120 Just like the Fibonacci sequence, this is one of the basic forms of exercise used in programming and is commonly used to introduce recursion.</description></item><item><title>Fibonacci Sequence</title><link>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/programming-tutorials/fibonacci-sequence/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:12:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/programming-tutorials/fibonacci-sequence/</guid><description>The Fibonacci sequence is a series of numbers where a number is the addition of the last two numbers. This is one of the basic forms of exercise used in programming and is almost always present in a programming exam. Therefore, learning how to print the Fibonacci sequence is essential to anyone learning programming or a new programming language.
0 1 1 2 3 5 8 13 21 34 55 89 144 233 377 Typically, there are two implementations of the Fibonacci sequence - (1) the iterative algorithm and (2) the recursive algorithm.</description></item><item><title>CentOS 7 VirtualBox 5.2 Error</title><link>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/virtualbox/centos-7-virtualbox-5-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/virtualbox/centos-7-virtualbox-5-2/</guid><description>Issue A recent linux kernel update (3.10.0-693.2.2.el7.x86_64) caused the VirtualBox Guest Additions 5.2 in my CentOS7 box to break.
Error message:
/tmp/vbox.0/hgsmi_base.c: In function ‘hgsmi_send_caps_info’: /tmp/vbox.0/hgsmi_base.c:99:2: error: implicit declaration of function ‘AssertRC’ [-Werror=implicit-function-declaration] AssertRC(p-&amp;gt;rc);^M ^ cc1: some warnings being treated as errors make[2]: *** [/tmp/vbox.0/hgsmi_base.o] Error 1 make[1]: *** [_module_/tmp/vbox.0] Error 2 make: *** [vboxvideo] Error 2 More information is in this virtualbox thread
virtualbox ticket
Resolution An updated VirtualBox Guest Additions installer which contains the fix can now be downloaded from the virtualbox website.</description></item></channel></rss>