<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Version Control on Don Figuerres</title><link>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/version-control/</link><description>Recent content in Version Control on Don Figuerres</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 23:15:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://donfiguerres.com/posts/version-control/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Global gitignore File</title><link>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/version-control/git/global-gitignore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 23:15:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/version-control/git/global-gitignore/</guid><description>When working with a version control system, you normally have files that are not ignored in some projects but you would like to ignore in globally in your workstation environment. The ways to do that are listed below.
Option 1: The git/ignore file in the home directory The user&amp;rsquo;s ignore file is mentioned briefly in the Git documentation. You can add here your ignore rules the same way as you do it with your project .</description></item><item><title>Git Connection Errors During Cloning</title><link>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/version-control/git/git-connection-errors-during-cloning/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 17:18:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/version-control/git/git-connection-errors-during-cloning/</guid><description>I got these errors recently when I was trying to clone one of our repos. Unstable network connection or network infrastructure may have caused this so as a workaround, you can clone the repo &amp;ldquo;bit-by-bit&amp;rdquo;.
$ git clone ssh://git@your.host.com/yourrepo.git Cloning into &amp;#39;projectdir&amp;#39;... ... remote: Enumerating objects: 26639, done. remote: Counting objects: 100% (269/269), done. remote: Compressing objects: 100% (152/152), done. client_loop: send disconnect: Connection reset by peer6 MiB/s fetch-pack: unexpected disconnect while reading sideband packet fatal: fetch-pack: invalid index-pack output $ git clone ssh://git@your.</description></item><item><title>Changing Committer, Author, and Email in Git</title><link>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/version-control/git/changing-committer-author-and-email-in-git/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:12:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://donfiguerres.com/posts/version-control/git/changing-committer-author-and-email-in-git/</guid><description>I recently observed in my GitHub profile that most of my commits are not shown in my contribution activity. After doing a quick search, I found that the problem because my email in my commits do not match the email associated with my GitHub account.
Changing Commits in the Remote Repository You need to use the filter-branch command to change the emails and names.
git filter-branch -f --env-filter &amp;#39; GIT_AUTHOR_NAME=&amp;#34;yourname&amp;#34;; GIT_AUTHOR_EMAIL=&amp;#34;youremaill@host.</description></item></channel></rss>